Anyways,
[music]
okay. So, let's look at um a lesson.
Here are some things you could be doing
wrong. Overtrading, uh over risking, and
we're going to go FOMOing in. These are
all the all the problems that you have.
Low win rate, revenge trading. Hey, that
would be overtrading. So, we can also
put that under here. Revenge trading,
missing trades. Okay, so this is what I
have on my list. What else we got?
Winners turn [music] to losses. So,
closing early. Okay, I like this. Good
stuff, boys. I'll say not closing
losses. Okay, so you guys are going to
love what I'm doing here. Okay, these
are all the the the problems you see in
trading. Okay, but I'm going to break
them down. We're going to do some of
these together, too. We're going to find
a solution for you. We're going to find
an actionable way that you can fix these
problems and wh why are you causing
these problems? Okay, you have to
analyze it appropriately. You can do
this exact same sort of routine to help
you determine what you should be doing
to fix that problem. Okay, so I have a
problem where I'm overtrading and it's
causing me to lose money. But what is
the the deeper issue between
overtrading? And that includes revenge
trading cuz revenge trading is
overtrading. The deeper issue and
hopefully you guys understand is poor
emotional control. If you are
overtrading, it means you you're not
able to sit on your hands. So, you are
getting excited about opportunities and
thus have poor emotional control. So,
how do you fix holding yourself back?
Meditation. You have to meditate every
single day. Practice meditation. Get
better at sitting and doing nothing
because then you're going to be able to
hold yourself back. That's the fix. I
know it sucks. You don't want to
meditate. Too [__] bad, dude. You
want to make money? Do you want to be a
good trader? This is how you do it,
dude. You make charts with problems that
you have. You guys don't want to learn
this stuff. I know it. You guys want to
learn the strategy that [__] makes
you rich. But this is what is actually
going to be helpful to you. So the next
one, overrisking. You're overrisisking
and then every once in a while you just
blow a massive amount of money. So what
is the problem there? What's the deeper
issue? Is you're a cocky douchebag. You
think that you're right. You think
you're smart. You're not. Let me let me
just remind you. You're not. You're not.
You're not smart enough. What's the
solution? gratitude. A lot of people can
pray your gratitude to your friends and
family. Things like this, right? These
things will then humble you, put you
down off your pedestal. That's what
you're trying to do here is if you're
overrisking, you're a very cocky
douchebag. And what you need to do is
knock yourself down a peg. Okay, next
one. FOMO or patience. It's also
emotional control. So, the solution once
again is uh meditation or limit your
trading. This can be a swing trading or
one trade a day. So slow down, [music]
right? So slow down. All these problems,
the solution is to do the opposite of
what you're trying to do. So next, poor
win rate. Okay, so here's one that you
actually might be interested in. If your
win rate is low, you have a bad
strategy. There are issues in trading
that have nothing to do with your
psyche, and this is one of them. How do
you know you have a a good strategy?
Back test. So, this is this is the only
one that's kind of a normal thing to
hear. If your back test doesn't show you
have like a 70% win rate, don't trade
the strategy. Okay, next one. Missing
trades. What is the underlying problem
from missing trades? Scared. Somebody
else says scared. Somebody else says
fear. Oh, I love you guys. These are
these This is perfect. These are the
perfect words. Hesitation, fear. Lack of
confidence. Oh, yeah. You guys got it.
Those are all the banging words I wanted
to hear. What is the solution? Practice
bravery. You're hesitating. you're
uncomfortable and you're unable to take
action in uncomfort. So, it's the
opposite of FOMOing. Too much holding
you back, too much telling you not to
pull the trigger. You need to speed up.
Maybe what you want to do is force one
trade per day. Make sure that you take
one trade per day or maybe make sure
that you do something that scares you
every day. So, winners turn to losers.
Greed. Yeah, good one. Uh
ungratefulness. [__] yeah, bros. So, why
did you not close basically, right? So
the fix you could spend less, right?
That's another good one. Try to budget
less so that you don't feel the need to
be making so much money and you need
once again humbleness. Okay, next one.
So if you're closing early, there's one
of two things happening. You're worried
it's going to reverse on you and you
want to lock in that profit. You want to
lock in that, oh, I was right. So what
is the problem with needing to feel
right? So I'm going to reward this to
needing to feel right. Well, it's an ego
problem again. How do we remove the ego
attachment that we have? We identify as
traders. If we perform poorly in the
trading world, our ego is damaged and we
are then seen as a worse person through
our own eyes. So the way that we remove
that ego is to create other hobbies. So
I don't need to feel like my identity is
completely based around feeling right.
Okay. So closing late is I think is the
same thing. Greed and then not closing
losses. Again, needing to feel right.
You don't want to be wrong. So, these
are all very similar. And then those
ones up top are very similar. This is a
trading channel. That entire hour, I
didn't [__] look at the chart cuz I
don't care, dude. And that's the mindset
that you go into these things. It's
super super simple once you have like
this kind of aloof mentality. And if you
look at this overtrading, over risking,
FOMO, all these fast-paced things that
the the the idea is I want money quick.
The solution is slowing down, doing some
meditative stuff, you know, practicing
that peaceful world, right? [music]
And then this is the only one that has
anything to do with actual trading is if
you're not winning. And this is the only
one that people struggle with if they're
too scared. A lot of this stuff is also
nested in here, too. Overrisking is is
an ego thing, too. A lot of those are
overlapped, but in other words, try to
be a better person. That's funny. Yeah.
The hilarious thing with all of these
things is slow down your life. Be a
calm, peaceful person with a lot of
activities and a really awesome life.
Isn't that crazy? Actually, if you look
at this, the only thing that has nothing
to do with with just being a really
awesome person is if you have a low win
rate. [laughter]
If you're just not winning at all,
that's the only time where the solution
is to actually try to trade more.
Everything else is like, hey, I should
go outside and go fishing. That's
[__] sick, dude. I caught a fish
today. I took one trade in the morning
and then went fishing. That's what made
me a better trader. Wow. I have a
[__] sick life. And isn't that what
trading is about? Isn't that the whole
point of trading? Is to make a really
awesome life where you have a lot of
freedom. Wow. Oh my god, it's so fun.
Yeah. All right, boys. Um, I'm going to
take a screenshot of that and I'm going
to post that in the Discord. Uh, I'm
going to turn off the live stream now.
Okay. See you guys. It's all about
freedom, baby.